朽木字幕组
翻译：
飞越无限
校对：
压制：
飞越无限
你们想知道我们什么时候营业么  Tess?
You want to know when we're gonna open, Tess?
Well 当我和Johnny说营业时候才会开门营业
Well, we're gonna open when me and Johnny fucking say so.
你们三个 像秃鹰一样在AI的门外徘徊
And you three, hovering around like buzzards outside Al's door...
不会有任何的作用的
will not hasten the situation.
都已经日上三竿了 AI也没说要罢市啊
It was fucking sun-up before Al called it quits.
现在  他已经在示威了
Now, he has earned a sleeping-in.
Dan  当他离开他的办公室的时候他才锁门
He locks the door, Dan, when he leaves his office.
AI在里面时候他不锁门 [现在门是锁着的]
Al does not lock the door when he's inside.
那只是惯例中的例外
That's just the exception that proves the fucking rule.
我猜也是
I suppose.
我可以问下么 Wolcott先生
May I ask, Mr Wolcott,
是什么吸引你来到了我们这儿的?
what purpose draws you to our hills?
-黄金 -黄金? 我明白了
-Gold. -Gold? I see.
-早上好  Utter先生 -早上好
-Morning, Mr Utter. -Morning.
他常常光顾我的自助餐
Frequents my buffet religiously.
好吧 我想留在这弄些土地证明
Yes, I hope to locate and secure an assortment of claims.
各式各样的?
An assortment?
好买卖 这让我感觉您不是第一干这行了
Shrewd hedging, which makes me think this is not your first parade.
如果是呢 我不记得我告诉过你
If it was, I don't suppose I'd admit it to you.
只是证实一下我的猜测
Only confirming my original impression.
去拿他的行李
Get his luggage.
-我的店员会安置您的物品的 -多谢
-My staff will install your possessions. -I thank you.
你买粮食了
You bought provisions.
在晚上我等你回家的时候买的
During the night, while I was waiting for you to come home.
-这是个24小时营业的营地 -我知道
-It's a 24-hour camp. -So I saw.
我对我昨天说的一些事感到抱歉
Certain things I said yesterday I regret.
如果你把它当做耳旁风我会很感激的
I'll be grateful if you'd not rely on them.
好吧
All right.
我所说的 关于写信内容的事
Representations I made as to letters I'd written.
实际上我并没有写在信里
I didn't.
如果你没信我所说的收到了那些信  我也会很高兴
I'll be grateful, then, if you'll not rely on my assurance that I got them.
好吧
All right.
[首先邮差总会弄丢信件 所以写没写只有男的知道
他可以撒谎  女的就假装自己收到了]
我致以我最诚挚的感谢  Bullock先生
I'll hold my deepest gratitude, Mr Bullock...
为我们现在的生活
for what will let us live as we are now.
-燕麦粥看起来有点老  -确实是 不是么?
-This oatmeal looks old. -lt does, doesn't it?
Richardson  该死的  燕麦粥糗了
Richardson, God damn you! The oatmeal is clotted.
都熬好2小时15分钟了
There's 45 minutes yet till the three hours.
别胡说八道了  赶紧换一个
Stop spouting gibberish and replace the damned oatmeal.
我用培根对付一顿吧
I'll make do with the bacon.
像这样的营地…
A camp like this...
只能从小地方找仆人
one draws one's menials from a small and brackish pool.
一旦猪肉吃完了 [培根是猪肉]
Once the pig is digested...
也许我们可以想点别的什么事 [比如生意]
perhaps we could pursue a possibility that's come to mind.
如果你仍然这么殷勤的话  当然可以
If the spirit still moves in you, sure.
-也许我们现在就可以了 -不
-Maybe we could do it now? -No.
也许我们要先让你的思想成熟起来
Let's let your mind ripen and mature the possibly first.
昨晚我在看到的在外面的那个人
The creature I saw outside our place last night...
就是你说是市长的那个人
who you said is the camp's mayor...
现在正像秃鹰一样守着那个吃早饭的人
now perches like a vulture over that man at breakfast.
当然 肯定地
Of course. Certainly.
Farnum  他拥有这家旅馆
Farnum. He owns the hotel.
-你喜欢Farnum市长么? -一点都不喜欢
-Have you affection for Mayor Farnum? -None.
很好
Good.
因为市长想忽悠的那个人…
Because the man the Mayor expects to digest...
伪装了起来  要戏耍Farnum先生
is going to toy and play with Mr Farnum from camouflage...
只要他觉得好玩就会一直玩下去
for as long as he finds it amusing...
最终把市长大人变成他的美餐
and then make him a meal of his own.
-那人是谁? -一个骗子
-Who is the man? -A trick.
还是 个中高手
A specialist...
他让人叫他W先生
who asks to be called Mr W.
E.B.Farnum请求进入许可
E.B. Farnum demanding entry.
-叫下AI  -叫不到他
-Summon Al. -He's not summonable.
为了我带来的消息  他肯定会被叫出来的
For the news I bear, he'll be plenty summonable.
为什么你不自己上去叫他呢 EB?
Why don't you go on up and summon him yourself, E.B.?
荣幸之至
Happily.
他在门后
He's behind lock and key.
你确定他在里面么?
You're certain he's within?
对于我的敲门  他回应‘给我他妈地滚蛋’
Called out to my knock. Said, "Get the fuck away."
衣冠不整当然要谨慎点或者打点好
Fornication demanding discretion or a bribe.
他单独待着呢 他会一直待下去
He's fucking alone and he's gonna stay that way...
-直到他想开了  -我认为他是身体不舒服
-until he chooses to be otherwise. -I think he's fucking poorly.
Well  他的声音都变的沙哑了
Well, his voice has got a gravelly timbre.
-想留个口信么? -事实上 是的 我想留
-Want to leave a message? -ln fact, I do. Yes.
AI  如果你你还没死到发烂
"Al, if you're not dead and already mouldering...
我送来了一个能让你复苏的消息
"l send news to revive you.
一条比得上利维坦的肥鱼已经游到我们的水域
"A fish to rival the fabled Leviathan has swum into our waters.
赶紧好起来  我们好一起逮住他
"Get well soon and we'll land the cocksucker together.
你的朋友 EB
"Your friend, E.B."
你可以加句附言
You might add as a postscript...
我也有你派我去打探的
"l also have the news you dispatched me to secure...
有关新到的妓女的信息
"of the newly-arrived cunt."
劳烦了
Please.
-你刚搬到这来? -昨天刚到
-You just move here? -Just yesterday.
我看到治安官建造了这所房子
I watched the Sheriff build this house.
Bullock是我爸爸的弟弟
Mr Bullock's my pa's brother...
在我父亲死后娶了我母亲
that married my mum when my pa got killed.
所以现在他既是我爸爸又是我叔叔
So now he's my pa and my uncle.
大鳟鱼生活在那边的深水区下面
Big trout lives in that deep part down there.
-Damon! -就来了
-Damon! -Coming!
我和爸爸要去俄勒冈州种苹果树
My pa and me are going to grow apples in Oregon.
-你会回来么? -爸爸说我们不会再回来了
-Will you come back? -Pa says we ain't never coming back.
注意那边的彩虹  我叫他Jumbo
Keep your eye on that rainbow. I call him Jumbo.
早上好  William
Morning, William.
早上好   Bullock先生
Morning, Mr Bullock.
-你拿回了你的东西  -我拿回来了
-You got your gun and badge back. -I did.
我把他们放在了那个篮子里以便你能看到
I put them in that basket for you to see.
-你又和那个男的打架了么? -不 我们不必再打了
-Did you fight that man again? -No, we didn't have to fight.
那个男孩要去俄勒冈了
That boy is going to Oregon.
那边的溪流下游有鳟鱼在游荡
There's a trout loiters just downstream there.
那个男孩叫他Jumbo
The boy calls him Jumbo.
也许下班后…
Maybe after work...
我们会让它为自己的懒散付出代价
we can make him pay for his slothful ways.
Ellsworth先生 开采的规模…
Does the scope of the find, Mr Ellsworth...
需要的粉碎机远不止现在用的这台5辊的吧?
warrant more than the five-stamp mill we operate with now?
Oh 没问题 夫人 [想想四缸发动机就明白了]
Oh, no question, ma'am.
你的矿区需要25辊的 很容易买到
Your holdings justify 25 stamps, easy.
就是要先等法律上的问题被解决掉
Just a matter of waiting till the legalities get resolved.
为什么买粉碎机还要法律允许?
And why would the purchase of a larger machine await legal resolution?
Well 夫人  因为没有法律允许…
Well, ma'am, 'cause without title...
你就没有原料喂你的25辊粉碎机
you wouldn't own no quartz for your 25-stamp machine to crush.
-早上好 Bullock先生  -早上好
-Good morning, Mr Bullock. -Morning.
-早上好  Sofia  -早上好
-Good morning, Sofia. -Good morning.
-Garret夫人去矿场了 -是么.
-Mrs Garret has gone to see her claim. -Has she?
-是的 和Ellsworth.先生一起 -我明白了
-Yes, with Mr Ellsworth. -I see.
她要求 如果我看到你 就把这个还给你
She asked, if I saw you, please to give you this back.
-Sofia可以用另一个表学习 -好吧
-Sofia can learn on another watch. -All right.
时机合适时  你可以询问一下Garret夫人…
When opportunity permits, you might inquire of Mrs Garret...
因为营地里的孩子越少越好
as few children as are in the camp
我明白你的意思了 Bullock先生
I take your meaning, Mr Bullock.
如果甲方感觉合适…
If she decided it was appropriate...
乙方也会欣慰、感激
other parties would be delighted and grateful.
-好的 well 但愿她会决定那么做  -好的
-Yes, well, she will have to decide that. -Yes.
营地拳击手
The camp pugilist.
因为我喜欢你 Joanie…
Fond as I am of you, Joanie...
否则我不会把自己和姑娘们都带到这里来
I wouldn't have brought my girls and my own tired ass out here...
只是凭着你的善意的邀请函
on just your kind invitation.
那个骗子的到来让前景变好了么? W先生?
The trick sweetened the prospect? Mr W?
他曾经对我的一个姑娘说要带她来这儿
He offered on one of my girls to bring her out here.
因为W先生是
Being as Mr W is...
George Hearst的首席管家
chief lookout for George Hearst...
后者在Comstock和Mexico受到和很大的打击
that struck biggest in the Comstock and Mexico...
我知道他[乔治]很看好这个营地的未来
I knew he'd just endorse the camp's future.
W的短板是他喜欢和他的女人玩性游戏
Short side, Mr W enjoys being cranky with his women.
但不高兴的时候  他的趣味就荡然无存了
But sometimes when disappointed his crankiness runs away with him.
什么会惹她不高兴?
What's gonna disappoint him?
非光明正大的手段
Devious sort that I am...
我有他肯定会感兴趣的姑娘
I've got the girl he's interested in on ice.
-多谢 -Wolcott先生…
-Thank you. -Mr Wolcott...
我是管理者 而非所有者
I'm the custodian, note I do not say "owner"...
Wild Bill Hickok在世时最后信件的管理者
of Wild Bill Hickok's final earthly communication.
湿了
It's damp.
Wolcott先生  在给我这封信之前不到一个小时
Mr Wolcott, not an hour before giving me the letter...
Bill透漏给我 他发现了个矿脉
Bill confided to me, having come upon a quartz deposit...
他许诺 用他自己的话说 ‘不计其数的财富’
promising, in Bill's own words, "wealth beyond counting."
那是多少财富呢? 我不知道 Wolcott先生
How much wealth is that? I don't know, Mr Wolcott.
我不知道Bill最多计算到了多少
I don't know how high Bill could count.
你想要我付多少钱?
How much do you want me to pay?
我没想让你付钱  反而
I'd hardly expect you to pay anything. Imagining rather...
我会支付你的花销
I will pay you your cost...
只为了把信送到合适的人手里
to see the letter delivered to its proper recipient.
我加100元
Plus $100...
来阻止你从信上获益
set against whatever profits you may generate...
可能送信是不可能了
should delivery prove impossible...
从信里所包含的信息上看
from the information the letter contains.
那么这信被拿出来
So this is set off...
又不想让我从这件事中获益
against profits I might gain in the event that this letter...
而这封信证明是无法送达的 又包含如此珍贵的信息
proving undeliverable, contains such valuable information.
-你脑袋里有个数字么? -1万美金
-Have you an amount in mind? -$10,000.
-你会付我100美元? -正确
-Less the $100 you would pay me? -Correct.
-那我就应该付你9千9百美元 -是的
-$9,900 net then, me to you? -Yes.
我现在就给你钱  在送信之前?
And I would pay you that now, before attempting the letter's delivery?
Oh  是的
Oh, yes.
你一旦拥有这封信 我就与它无关了
Once you have the letter, all my connection to it is severed.
-我明白 -送不送信
-I see. -To deliver it or not...
或者你想干什么
or whatever the hell you wanted to do.
-你马上就能拿到钱  -好的
-Well, you will have my decision shortly. -Fine, then.
-搬行李的小费 -Oh 不 我不会接受的
-For the luggage. -Oh, no, I wouldn't hear of it.
这是我的荣幸
It was my great pleasure.
我相信我一会儿就能收到你的消息的
I trust I will hear from you soon.
我现在明白了付出怎样的代价才把你带回我的生活
I see now what it takes to bring you back into my life.
-我只是路过而已 Star先生 -即便如此…
-Just passing through, Mr Star. -Even so...
仍然让还有三肢键好的男人很是高兴
it makes a man glad he has three limbs left to be damaged.
早上好
Morning.
一个男人花5美元就能把我带进他的生活
A man can get me in his life with $5.
如果只要手活的话 是2美元
$2 if he just needs a handshake.
-早上好 -早上好
-Good morning. -Morning.
早上好
Morning.
Trixie.
多谢
Many thanks.
-还疼么?  -没事了
-How bad does that pain? -It's all right.
-我住在我的房子里 -和Martha还有孩子一起?
-I'm in my house, Sol. -With Martha and the boy?
我选择不把她们扔在大道上
Chose not to put them in the thoroughfare.
或者说我明白你要问啥
Or, I see what you're asking...
至于她会有别的什么想法 对于我曾经泄露出的信息 也许会吧?
far as her having a different opinion, possibly, once I showed up?
不 她选择留下来
No, she chose to stay.
well 很好
Well, good.
-不管咋样 你开张么? -当然
-Anyways, could you open up? -Sure.
很感激
Glad to.
-要人帮你么? -不用 我很好
-Any help with your person? -No, I'm all right.
Swearengen说郡特派员都来自杨克顿
Swearengen said county commissioners are all from Yankton.
什么时候的事?
When was this?
就在我们打架前
Just before we hit the mud.
没有本地山里的代表就不对了
It's wrong the hills get no representation.
即便在伊甸园  错误有时也会发生
Even in an Eden like this, wrongs sometimes occur.
我是说也许我们应该做点什么
I meant, maybe we should try to do something about it.
我支持你
I'm with you.
该死的 AI
God damn it, Al!
正如现在这样 离这么远我没法开整
Such as they are, my arts cannot be practised at this remove.
别耍孩子气了
Stop being a baby!
你想保守的隐私
Any secrets that you feel need keeping...
不会被我泄露的
will not be betrayed by me.
-医生? -Trixie
-Doc? -Trixie.
休息吧  不会被打扰地
Rest, uninterrupted.
没有拜访 没有例外
No visits, no exception.
因为和Bullock打架打输了 还是他的阴茎出问题了?
From his fray with Bullock he's poorly, or it's trouble with his prick?
如果你让他同意我进去
If you can get him to grant you entry...
也许你就能告诉我了
maybe you'll confide that to me?
我是Trixie
It's Trixie...
我听到了医生的话 [指不让人进去]
that's overheard the Doc's instruction.
所以我就在这儿大声说出消息了
So let me just shout my information from here.
没人死亡
Nobody's dead.
Bullock去了他造的那所房子
Bullock's gone to that house he built.
Star也多多少少能自己站起来了
Star is on his feet, more or less.
无论如何我会继续在五金店打探消息
Anyways, I'm gonna stay on the ear over to the hardware store.
Yeah.
AI  下件事是 该死的电线杆
Fucking telegraph poles, Al...
被立在了大道上
are next thing to landed in the fucking thoroughfare.
人类的下一个进步的产物  它们要到这里了
Next leap of the creature, they'll be here.
好了 AI
All right, Al.
-Dolly在哪呢? -做生意呢
-Where's fucking Dolly? -Fucking.
她上一次和他做是什么时候的事?
When was she last with him?
破晓时分 就是在归还Bullock东西之前
Daybreak, just before he give Bullock back his iron.
在她伺候过他之后 我们都见过AI
We've seen him after she did.
你给他沏点茶
You brew him my fucking tea.
放在托盘上 带给他 让他喝了
Put it on a tray, you take it up to him and make him fucking drink it.
好的
All right.
如果他不露面 几个小时后
If he don't present himself in a few hours...
撞开门  带医生进去
kick down the door and get the fucking Doc in there.
我是Lila 欢迎到贝拉联盟
I'm Lila. Welcome to the Bella Union.
我叫 Francis Wolcott
And I'm Francis Wolcott...
我会很感激的  如果你叫一下你的老板
which I'd be grateful if you'd tell your employer.
这是 Francis Wolcot,Cy
This is Francis Wolcott, Cy.
我是Cy Tolliver,Wolcott先生
Cy Tolliver, Mr Wolcott.
你好 你喝点什么?
How do you do, and what'll you drink?
肯塔基波本威士忌 如果你有的话
Kentucky bourbon if you got it.
给Wolcott先生倒杯波本威士忌 Jack
Pour Mr Wolcott a bourbon, Jack,
然后告诉他是肯塔基产的
and tell him it's from Kentucky.
-肯塔基波本威士忌 不加冰? -是的 麻烦了
-Kentucky bourbon. Straight up? -Please.
我们要让Lila做陪么?
Shall we have Lila drink with us...
还是你想和Lila单独喝?
or would you like to drink with Lila alone?
我更愿意我们俩私下谈谈
I would rather we two converse privately.
只是谈谈么 先生  我可不是GAY
Just talk now, sir? I'm not that kind of fellow.
也许你只是在等合适的呢
Maybe you're just waiting for the right offer.
游戏快结束了  但我猜一切皆有可能
It's late in the game, but I suppose anything is possible.
你想出来一下么?
Will you take the air?
如果我要失贞  我宁可是在外面
If I'm to lose my virtue, I'd as soon do it outside these walls.
你在旧金山找过一个组织
You approached a group in San Francisco...
那个组织和我的老板有生意往来
that does business with my employer.
你这段话真得加快了我的信任 [反话]
That group-and-employer bullshit really quickens me with fucking trust.
你找的团体是个友好的中国组织
That group you've approached is a fraternal Chinese organisation.
‘堂口’可不是什么好词
"Tong" is not a clever enough word?
你提供给他们一个送人来此营地的合同
You offered them a contract to send members to this camp.
那个组织和我的老板有一个
That organisation has a pre-existing arrangement...
早就计划好的安排
with my employer.
那么你为谁工作呢 Wolcott
So you work for who, Wolcott?
铁路公司 偷渡亚洲人的…
The railroads, some mining combination...
采矿联合会?[包含着华人劳工寓意]
that brings those slant-eyes in by the boatload?
不 先生 我是为一个人工作 而不是组织
No, sir. I work for one man.
上帝啊  我们不都是么?[他理解为 人不为己]
Jesus Christ! Doesn't every one of us?
George Hearst.
我之前的话 从我们见面到现在说的话
I meant no disrespect of any kind to you or Mr Hearst...
对您和Hearst先生没有任何的恶意
by any word I've said from the moment we have met.
我理解
I understand that.
在康斯托克和蒙大拿 我很尊敬Hearst先生
I have nothing but respect for Mr Hearst in the Comstock and Montana...
在其他的他经营过的地方我也没有任何的不敬
every other place he's ever operated, without jape or jest.
你在旧金山给那个组织的提案
And the overture you made to the group in San Francisco...
展现的预见力和想象力
showed imagination and foresight...
以及风险估计 都给Hearst先生很深的印象
and a tolerance for risk that was impressive to Mr Hearst.
我们想在这和你合作
We want to work with you here.
-你确定? -是的 我们确定
-You do? -Yes, we do.
Con Stapleton!  Leon!
Con Stapleton! Leon!
过来 见位绅士
Get over here and meet a fucking gentleman.
那两个人为我工作 安插在中国人群中
Those two work for me now among the Celestials...
好打击那个中国佬的傲慢态度
setting up that miserable cocksucker to get knocked off his high horse.
-Con, Leon. -我不想见他们
-Con, Leon. -I don't want to meet them.
进去吧
Go inside.
在里面见我
Meet me inside.
-好的 先生  -好的 先生 Tolliver先生
-Yes, sir. -Yes, sir, Mr Tolliver.
只管过去吧 伙计们
Just go on in, fellows.
我只和你联系
My only contact's with you.
至于他们所知道的  你和Hearst先生甚至不存在
As far as they're concerned, you and Mr Hearst don't even exist.
至于你要记住的是 Cy 在这件事中 你代表他
As far as you're concerned, Cy, in the task you'll be performing for him...
Hearst先生也会不知道这些
Mr Hearst doesn't either.
Hearst先生是谁呢?
Who?
[这段生意是非法的所以既要当婊子又要立牌坊]
起床了 你是在屋子里
Wake up. Take account you're indoors.
There.
-那个现在是水了 -拿一边儿去
-That's water, now. -Get it the fuck away from me, then.
别犯傻 喝了吧
Drink it and don't be stupid.
Oh 上帝啊 我们是被捕了么?
Oh, Christ, are we arrested?
我来向你解释一切 Jane 我是邮差
I explained all this to you, Jane, that I'm the fucking Deputy...
以防你回来我修好了这个漏雨的房间
and that I fixed up the overflow cell in case you come back.
闭嘴吧
Shut up, then.
你的回答就是‘我烦透了你说的’
And you replied I was boring the shit out of you...
‘因为医生已经告诉了你所有的事’
'cause Doc already told you all about it.
Well  很明显 我都不记得了
Well, evidently, I don't remember fuck-all.
不 因为在昨晚我们一起经历了所有事情之后
No, 'cause after every other fucking thing we went through last night...
你让我们站在了面对着英国佬的路口上
you got to make us stop at that new joint across from Nuttall's.
你能闭上你的嘴么?
Would you kindly shut your fucking mouth?
Hey Bill的衣服怎么在这里?
Hey, what the fuck's Bill's coat doing here?
Well 他不会愿意看到这个没人用被当作纪念品的
Well, he wouldn't have seen it useless or a souvenir.
我让它发挥点余热
I figured I'd give it work keeping the bed warm.
现在我是它的主人了么?
Where is it headed now I'm the occupant?
它不会去别的地方的
It ain't going anywheres.
谢谢 Charlie.
Thank you, Charlie.
天气不冷 坐在外面吧
It's cool. Sit outside.
漏点肉
Wide knees.
我们是要争论么?
Are we gonna argue?
我们是拍档 不是么 Maddie?
We're partners, ain't we, Maddie?
很多计划和想法都不让你的拍档参与么?
Ain't that a lot of planning and thinking to not let your partner in on?
在我了解那个诡计之前我不会分享它
Not sharing it before I even knew the trick was in camp...
别逼我做错事 Joanie
don't put me wrong, Joanie.
抛弃信任 也不会让你干对的事
It don't put you right, far as an atmosphere of trust.
Joanie (我来告诉你)会发生什么当我们都出去了
Joanie, was there any odds when me and my girls got out here...
你可能会告诉我你改变主意了
that you might have told us you'd changed your mind?
我感觉这是个机会
I guess there was a chance.
或者我发现你死了 或者一切如常的断续下去
Or I'd have found you dead or moved along?
没有机会继续下去的
No chance on moved along.
唯一能有确定折结果的路就是当妓女 honey
Only way to guarantee an outcome, honey, is contracting to be fucked.
其他的每件事都是一个机会
Everything else is a chance...
包括我让你失望
including me letting you down.
如果是我在尝试 至少由我出头不会被警告
But if I do, using my head won't be the tip-off.
你怎么带着姑娘参与进去?
How will you bring the girl into it?
要在那个骗子的强烈坚持之下
-At the trick's fierce insistence.
-怎么分成 -五五开
-What's our split? -Fifty-fifty.
-那个姑娘的结局呢? -我不排除弄个棺材
-What's the girl's end? -I wouldn't rule out a wooden box.
赶紧买吧 这是我们最后的存货
Timely purchase. It's our last in stock.
该死的 我自己忘了考虑以小订单重新供应了
Goddamn out-thinking myself, re-supplying in smaller orders.
你已经处理了一些不确定性
You've been dealing with a few uncertainties.
如果所有的合同(矿山买卖)被通过 或者不被通过
If the claims get allowed or they don't...
以及杨克顿派不派特派员
or Yankton stacks the commissioners or not...
我们做生意或者不做生意 [以上列举风险项]
we're either in business or we ain't...
如果我们做生意 通过按量购买你减少了成本
and if we are, you reduce costs buying in volume.
-你父亲教你的? -在维也纳他临终之际
-Your old man? -On his deathbed in fucking Vienna.
伙计们 情况渐好啊
Fellows. On the mend?
好多了 谢谢了 也祝愿你
Doing better, thank you. Hope you are, too.
我们昨天正要完成这些问询
We was gonna thin these inquiries yesterday...
在bummer Dan的麻烦之前
before that trouble with bummer Dan.
我们完成这件事要好几个星期呢
We've been going to thin them for several weeks.
Farnum的破房子还好么?
Farnum's slop-house okay?
Jane在我的房子里安心睡着了
Jane's sleeping a load off at my place.
来自其他辖区的问询 我们有点怠慢了
Inquiries from other jurisdictions. We've been somewhat remiss.
那话咋说来着 明日复明日
Who is that fellow said, "Never put off till tomorrow...
明日何其多
"what'll wait till the day after"?
(有很多罪犯逃往这里 新治安官要和全国的联系,类似引渡)
这个可不是我父亲说的
Not my old man.
-买Hickok的信 -很好
-To buy the Hickok letter. -Wonderful.
-要有卖契 -Well 当然可以 先生 当然
-I'll have a bill of sale. -Well, certainly, sir. Of course.
为了法律上好看
For reasons of legal nicety...
我们得说你买了送这封信的权力
we'll say you're purchasing the right to deliver.
你得让我拿夜壶啊 AI
You gotta let me get to your piss-pot, Al!
否则 等你心情不好的时候
Otherwise, when your mood changes...
你又要大喊我什么都不干了
you're fucking gonna yell at me for not doing it!
我认为我应该去找医生 AI
I think I should get the Doc, Al!
你需要医生进去
You need to let the Doc in!
你需要他诊治你
You need to let him see to you!
我生病的时候就是医生帮了我
When I was sick, the Doc helped me!
而且自从我的脚牵引上了你也没再吼我
And you ain't fucking yelled since then my foot's dragging!
-该死的 我这么做 对么?医生 -好吧
-Fuck this, right, Doc? -Fuck it.
Dan!
你应该把门撞开
You need to fucking break the door down!
-现在? -我说的你没听清么?
-Now? -lsn't that what I just fucking said?
Al!
如果我是你 医生 我就离远点
If I was you, Doc, I'd get out of the fucking way!
上帝啊
Jesus fucking Christ!
-你还好么? -我感觉我伤了我的肩
-You all right? -I think I broke my fucking shoulder.
打开我的药箱
Just open up my case.
AI?
Al?
Al, Al.
-我们要给他鸦片酒么? -请拿点吧
-Do we need to get him laudanum? -Please.
没事的 AI
All right, Al.
没事的 会好的
All right, it's all right.
在Stackpole的案子上请不要宽容
"Please don't let up on the Stackpole case...
我很肯定他跑到了你那儿
"as I'm sure he's out there."
-我不知道 -我也没听说过
-No idea. -I never heard of it either.
出于你总领全营地的角度 我犹豫是不是去打听一下
With all the portions you had on your plate, I hesitated to fucking inquire.
你打听了 我也不会帮这个治安官的
I couldn't have helped if you had.
那就去他妈的Stackpole案子吧
Fuck the Stackpole case, then...
那封来自Arapahoe郡的信也提到了
and the letter from Arapahoe County concerning it...
那就把它归于无效文件里吧
which goes in the fuck-case file.
我想买下Farnum先生的旅店
I'd like to buy Mr Farnum's hotel.
-干什么用呢 Garret夫人? -修修当我的住所
-To do what with, Mrs Garret? -To renovate and make my residence.
我能想到更好的房子 夫人 视野良好
I can think of better locations, ma'am, with friendlier views.
没有什么会比
None that would offer the further pleasure...
让Farnum先生流落街头更有意思
of putting Mr Farnum in the thoroughfare.
我预料Farnum那样的人很容易就能找个住处
I expect a man like Farnum finds quarters pretty easy.
我预料 即便满足他唯利是图的心 要是没了旅馆
I'd expect, even with his venality satisfied...
像Farnum那样的人也会感到身无分文 毫无着落
a man like Farnum would feel himself dispossessed and unanchored.
我认为他会很凄惨的
I think he'd be very sad.
并且我想看看他身处那种处境
And I'd like to see him in that condition.
我猜我们中的大部分人都很幸运
I guess most of us got enough luck...
虽穷却能按自己的想法行事
to be too broke to act on them type ideas.
你说的是什么想法?
What type ideas do you refer to?
就是穷人所说的当我们发怒我们就能得到的那种想法
The type the lowborn would say we get when we're pissed off.
尽管我的贵族血统
Although my own aristocratic lineage...
要我使用‘痛苦的失望’这个词
causes me to use the term "sore-disappointed."
我现在就生气了
I am pissed off.
Well 最后帮你一次  夫人 我得说你得到我的忠诚了
Well, last turns the wheel's took for you, ma'am, I'd say you've come by it honest.
如果打在某个人的鼻子上有用的话
If punching somebody in the nose would help...
我自愿当那个被打的人
I volunteer one that's well broke in.
安全返回
Safely returned.
-他也在么? -不在
-ls he here, too? -No.
-他是我朋友 Trixie -和其他操蛋的东西一样
-He's my friend, Trixie. -Among other fucking things.
不管怎样
Anyways.
我想 你能教我算账么?
I wondered, could you teach me to do accounts?
-好的 -我会付你钱
-All right. -I'll pay you.
或者你可以用钱交换和我造爱
Or you can take it out in cunt.
如果你一直这样的话 我不会教你
I won't teach you if you keep that up.
草你们所有人  我希望我是棵树
Fuck every fucking one of you. I wish I was a fucking tree.
-Mr Wolcott. -Mr Farnum.
信的内容让人非常失望
The contents of that letter are a deep disappointment.
没有一个词是提及发现或者宝藏有关的
Not a word of any find or promising location.
-那么你打开信了? -你在开玩笑么?
-You opened it then? -Are you trifling with me?
我突然想到 先生
It occurs to me, sir...
这段谈话最好换个地方
this conversation were best had elsewhere.
-但不能拖延时间? -不拖延 Mr Wolcott 不拖延
-But not postponed? -Not postponed, Mr Wolcott, no.
我们都是男人 先生
We are men, sir.
当我们意见不同 我们会很快解决
When we disagree, we come to resolution promptly.
-我们去哪? -Gem酒吧 就在那边
-Where are we going? -The Gem Saloon. It's just over there.
请从我肩上拿开你的手
Please take your hand off my shoulder.
一些意大利古语
Some ancient ltalian maxim...
适合我们的情形
fits our situation...
具体我忘了
whose particulars escape me.
重点是说我不走运么
Is the gist that I'm shit out of luck?
他们那么说了么?
Did they speak that way then?
Oh  为了上帝之爱啊
Oh, for the love of God!
不坐下么?
Please, won't you sit down?
那么你让我把这段经历
So you would have me take the experience then...
当做一次昂贵的教训?
as a lesson dearly purchased?
我应该告诉你Mr Wolcott
I should tell you, Mr Wolcott...
我在这个营地看到过很多人  都感到自己受害了
I have seen men in this very camp, feeling themselves victimised...
马上要求赔偿 我认为是比较轻率的
seek redress in fashions I thought imprudent.
你是说 要暴力一点?
Violently, you mean?
因此 在这
Thus, at the lesson...
昂贵的教训中学到的 你会受用 而我也能从此交易中脱身
dearly bought, as you would have it, is where I would leave this business.
无论如何 此次交易中我只是个中间人
In any case, I was an intermediary in this transaction.
那么就当个学生
Then, having been a pupil...
这事发生在你身上 会指导你的行为准则
it falls to you now to instruct your principal.
我很怀疑  Mr Wolcott
I wonder, Mr Wolcott...
如果第二封信不把你的教训
if some second letter couldn't be drafted...
写进去 [他可能是怕W写信告诉老板]
to put some sharper point on the lesson...
可能对我们俩都好
maybe remunerative to both of us.
所以你的意思就是我们要骗Hearst先生两次?
So, your idea would be that we fuck Mr Hearst twice?
我忘了他的名字了 先生 但一般来讲我会肯定地说
I missed the name, sir, but I can aver as a general principle...
我骗人的时间已经很长了
my days of fucking anyone are long in the past...
无论你代表谁
whomever you represent.
George Hearst 来自康斯托克的黄金开采商
George Hears，of the Ophir find in the Comstock.
当然 我知道George Hearst
Of course, I know George Hearst.
-Oh 你们有私交么? -我们没私交
-Oh, you know him personally? -I do not know him personally.
但是 我当然听说过George Hearst
But, of course, I know of George Hearst...
他的声望 成就 和财富
and his reputation and accomplishments and wealth...
以及他的势力和名誉
and his power and reputation.
我同样也要说 最重要的是
And I would say, as well, most importantly...
我没什么可以教给他的
I have nothing to teach that man.
George Hearst不需要从我这儿学任何东西
George Hearst need learn no lesson from me.
我也不会同意他来学一次
Nor would I permit him entrance into a lesson...
无论是非故意地或是偶然地
either inadvertently or by accident...
我也不会随后就立刻取消交易 让他背信
I wouldn't subsequently and immediately cancel him back out of.
对他的代理人或中间人也是如此
Or his agent or intermediary.
Hearst在合同上从不食言
Mr Hearst doesn't renege on contracts.
那么 我要做点什么?
Then, what am I to do?
我要做点什么呢 Mr Wolcott
What am I to do, Mr Wolcott...
除了承认这是场可怕的悲剧的错误
but to admit a terrible and tragic miscalculation...
然后我自己乞求谅解 理解和宽恕?
and take myself and beg mercy and understanding and forgiveness?
可以肯定的是 如果你考虑
And to aver, if you would contemplate...
其它的交易或者协议
any separate or side transaction or understanding.
从我前臂上拿开你的手 别再碰我
Remove your hand from my forearm. Do not touch me again.
我看起来很可怜
I look poor...
但这是有教养的姿态
but that is a cultivated pose and posture.
我不会可怜 也不会吝啬
I am not poor and I am not stingy...
当我的根本利益处于险境时
when fundamental interests are at stake.
算是个完整的旁白吧
As a complete aside.
你可以为Mr Hearst做件事
There is a service you could do Mr Hearst...
以抵销这次的这些钱上的损失
that would set off exactly against the funds...
否则他会认为你在当他好欺负
he might otherwise believe you fleeced him of.
什么事都行 先生
Anything, sir.
这件事就是征召你和其他一 两个人
This service would enlist you and one or two others...
制造有关营地未来的谣言
circulating certain rumours about the future of the camp.
尤其是 有关已有的土地证明的无效性上
In particular, about the validity of the present titles to the claims.
成交 算我一个吧
Done. Consider me enlisted.
把证明的合法性掺到问题里
Consider the validity called into question.
我也想知道你们的最高级的妓院在哪
I also wish to know the location of your highest-end brothel.
碰巧
As it happens...
一家妓院 无愧于这个名头的 刚刚开张
a whorehouse, succeeding to that title, has just opened.
没有碰巧  Mr Farnum
Nothing just happens, Mr Farnum.
你感觉这个帽子让我的头显得大么?
Do you think this hat makes my head look big?
不 先生
No, sir.
看上去正好
It makes your head look the perfect size.
多谢
Thank you.
你们要发掘出一点能力  包括你们自己
You're gonna find out something now about yourselves...
以及你们同伴 [提醒手下人]
and your fellow man.
你们怎样处理不幸的能力
How you handle adversity...
或者是关于不幸的谣言
or rumours of adversity...
或者坏运气 或者开始走背运
or ill fortune or turns of luck.
我不会推波助澜 或是制造谣言
And I'm not gonna further a rumour or be a party to that bullshit.
你想知道到时候我在哪么?
Do you want to know where I stand?
那你就看看到时候我在哪
You just look the fuck where I'm standing.
然后就会发现所有你要知道的东西
You'll find out all you need to know.
我哪儿都不会去的
I ain't going anywhere!
如果其他人想
And if anyone else wants to...
那么两个星期的禁闭在等着你呢
two weeks fucking severance is waiting for you right fucking now.
你站出来吧
You step the fuck up!
现在就站到右边吧
Step right the fuck up!
至少现在已经表明态度了
Now that shows me something.
但是任何时候 不管白天黑夜 有人动摇了
But anytime, day or night, anyone wants to fucking waver...
或者改变主意了
or fucking change their minds...
你就站到右边去领你的禁闭吧
you just step right the fuck up and get your severance.
那就开门吧 在能抓住的时候尽量把握住 好么?
Let's open the fuck up and get it while we can, all right?
-开门 -行动起来
-Open up! -Move, move, move!
-开门 -你听到他说什么了 来吧
-Open up! -You heard him, let's go!
你要对他做什么?
What are you gonna do to him?
把这个东西通过你的尿道插入膀胱
Pass this instrument through his penis into his bladder.
如果有结石 就会碰到这个金属器械上
If he has stones, it will click against the metal of the instrument.
假设在他尖叫声中我能分辨出碰撞声的话
Assuming I can hear the clicks above his screams...
我会诊断出尿道阻塞的原因
I will have identified the cause of his obstruction.
插到底?
To what fucking end?
插到底 要不是我认为他会死的话
To the end that if I think he will die...
我就切开外阴 拿出石头了
otherwise of cutting him open above the pubis and taking out the stones.
那样做却肯定会杀了他
Which will probably kill him anyways.
我要对你说什么呢 Trixie?
What shall I say to you, Trixie?
那样[也就是AI死了]对AI和我们都是个好的结果?
That I'm sure of a happy outcome for Al and every one of us?
-能给我们点时间么? Mr Tolliver -怎么了?
-Minute for us, Mr Tolliver? -What is it?
进来 关门
Come in and shut the door.
他妈的怎么了?
What the fuck is it?
你有事要交代我们么 Mr T?
Anything you want to tell us, Mr T?
我在外面已经告诉你们我想告诉你们的了
I told you all I want to tell you outside.
Well 相信我吧 我们俩不会是墙头草
Well, believe me, you don't have waverers standing in front of you...
或者立场不坚定的人 或者自找麻烦的人
or doubters, or anyone looking for a fucking severance.
-恰恰相反 -什么意思?
-Just the opposite. -What's that mean?
你们想升职?
You looking for a raise?
Well ‘怎么了’ 我猜这是Leon有这种疑惑 Mr Tolliver
Well, "What's going on?" I suppose is Leon's question, Mr Tolliver.
事实上 我的问题已经基本解决了
The truth is, my questions is answered 90%.
剩下的就是 给我点任务吧
And as for the rest, let me get good and fucking loaded...
好让落后者遭殃
and let the devil take the hindmost.
如果你走出这儿了 咱俩又要吵了
If you fucking walk out of here, us two are gonna have words.
就不只我刚才说的那些话
And more than words at my first opportunity...
因为来这里有9成是他的主意
because this was 90% his idea to come in here.
你们哪个最好解释下你们的真正意图
Somebody better turn over a hole card.
我们俩就是想给你个积极的印象 先生
Both of us took a real positive impression, sir...
刚才你给我们讲完话就直接进办公室了
off the talk you give us, just recently, here in your office.
与你刚才的总结性发言有关
Relative to this talk you just concluded.
还有?
And?
我猜你会和我们说出你的质疑
And I guess you'd say a wonderment with us...
比如是否我们忽略了说话的语调或者其他的什么
is if we mistook the tone of one talk or the other...
如果真的这样 是什么
and if so, which?
我质疑的是有件事改变了  就是两次谈话之间
I dispute that one fucking thing changed between those two talks as to...
我的态度和决心变了
my attitude and resolve.
营地的形势变化了么?
Did the facts of the camp situation change?
我也没有确切的把握
Not to my certain knowledge.
但如果你是在问我  私底下
But if you're asking, in the interim...
我得到了小道消息  是关于官方声明
have I been privy to a rumour, far as claims being invalidated...
所有签发的土地证明无效的 你要的答复是 是的
all titles thrown out, the answer is yes.
Well  这就是原因了
Well, that would account for it.
但是我意识到的事实是
But the only goddamn fact that I'm aware of is...
没有哪个男人靠谣言养活自己
I never knew any man ate a rumour or clothed himself with one...
或者嫖妓
or secured himself a piece of pussy.
Well  谣言毕竟不是事实
Well, rumours are not facts.
所以如果有没胆的混蛋
So if any gutless cocksucker...
忽然明白要发生什么了 决定要交割逃跑
tumbles to what's going on and decides he wants to cut and run...
卖掉他的财产
sell his fucking holdings...
你就告诉他来找我
you tell him to come see me.
就说Cy Tolliver会买他想卖的任何东西
Just say Cy Tolliver will buy whatever he's fucking selling...
如果他对营地没有信心
if he has that little faith in the camp...
就会产生有关无效性的谣言 以及随之而来的恐慌
or rumours of judicial invalidation, or the panic that'll ensue from that.
去吧 孩子们 出去做好你们的工作吧
Go ahead, boys. Go on outside and do your jobs.
那就是我们现在能做的  而不是动摇
That's all we can fucking do right now, and not waver.
进步了
Now that's fucking progress.
楼上的混蛋
Cocksucker upstairs...
大道对面 我工作的那个妓院
across the way, whorehouse where I work.
他是个混蛋
He is a fucking cocksucker.
锁上门 以为大家就不能帮他了
Locks the fucking door so people can't get to help him.
生病真可耻
Fucking ashamed to be sick!
你知道他曾经设计要杀死个孩子
You know he had a design to murder that little one.
-不 我不知道这事  -Hell 是的 他计划过
-No, I didn't. -Hell, yes, he had a design.
我和Charlie从营地里救走了她
Charlie and me spirited her from camp.
让他成为第二个受害者
Forced him to a second victim...
才配得上那个混蛋的目的
more suitable to his cocksucker's purpose.
想想会有影响么 如果人们的阴茎被切走?
Think they're any different if they've had their fucking dicks cut on?
还是有影响的
They ain't no fucking different.
你必须喜欢他们的朋友 要不他们不教你算帐
You gotta like their friends, or they won't teach you numbers...
还要遵守他们定的规则
or every other fucking regulation they set.
-不管怎么样的  -扯点远的
-Anyways. -Far as it fucking goes...
他把那个瘸子从孤儿院里带了出来
he also brought the cripple from that orphanage.
从哪个孤儿院?
From what orphanage?
别信他说的9美分的破事
And don't buy his bullshit about the nine-cent trick.
-哪个瘸子? -Jewel.
-What cripple? -Jewel.
他说他曾经反抗土豪的事
That he says he's got around against some hooplehead...
只是为了得到9美分 想找个妓女?
only having nine cents and wanting a piece of pussy？
才不是呢
That ain't it.
她生活在这的原因就是
Why she's around is...
这是他不擅长的保护她的方式
it's his sick fucking way of protecting her.
我要去弄瓶威士忌
I'm gonna get whiskey.
每件破事都有其两面性
There's entries on both side of the fucking ledger...
这才是重点 我已经像个祥林嫂了
is the fucking point, as I already talk like a fucking Jew.
一个美妙的夜晚要来临了
Shaping up to be a nice cool evening.
也许他也有好的一面
Maybe he has a good side to him, too...
却被我忽略了
that I entirely fucking missed.
这是有可能的 因为我总是在持续的醉酒之中
It's always fucking possible, drunk as I am, fucking continuously.
见到你很高兴
It's nice to see you.
-你归还了怀表? -是的
-You returned his timepiece? -Yes.
-我感觉我已经告诉你了 -是的 Miss lsringhausen
-I thought I'd told you. -You did, Miss lsringhausen.
我重提此话题 希望你不要介意
I'm recurring to the topic, hoping you will be more expansive.
他接受了怀表 夫人
He accepted the timepiece, ma'am...
还提了件事 也许我们俩应该换个时间再谈
and raised another subject you and l ought pursue at some different moment.
我必须要说你这个词用得好 lsringhausen小姐 我猜
Must I credit the right of that "ought," Miss lsringhausen, or may I suspect...
你挺喜欢制定条件的?
you enjoy setting terms?
条件 夫人?
Terms, ma'am?
就是由你来决定事情的时间和原因
Playing arbiter of the when and why of things.
提到Bullock先生的第二件事 Garret夫人
Pursuing the second subject Mr Bullock raised, Mrs Garret...
可能会让在场一个人不开心 她比咱俩都小
might upset a person now present, junior to you and me.
我想像不出来一个提议会有多么的让人不开心
I cannot imagine how such a pursuit could be any more upsetting...
比起你一直以来造成的
than the atmosphere of relentless disapproval...
冰冷的尴尬的气氛
that you so consistently generate.
我不需要你进一步的服务了  lsringhausen小姐
I've no further need of your services, Miss lsringhausen.
那我应该对你和Sofia说晚安了
I'll say goodnight, then, to you and Sofia.
我更倾向于是再见
My preference is your saying goodbye.
我想 夫人
I wonder, ma'am...
是否决定的太仓促了
if having made so many decisions so quickly...
你现在明显没有耐心去考虑此事
your patience may be short just now?
我请求你明早重新考虑一下你的决定
And I'd appeal to you to reconsider your preferences in the morning.
无论如何  你都要卷铺盖走人了
In any case, you'll want to retire to your room.
我希望你想想我是从芝加哥
I hope you'll recall that I've travelled from Chicago...
过来应职的  也没为发生这样的事而留条后路
to enter your employ and have no emergent prospects.
-我们会安排后面的事  -好吧
-We'll come to some arrangement. -All right.
-那我就祝你晚安了  -作为习惯
-I'll say goodnight, then. -As is your custom...
就不再给我孩子留一个申请的送别么?
without having spared one affectionate look for my child.
我所受的培训  夫人
My training, ma'am...
就是教好孩子
is that being engaged to see to the child's education...
我要是恳求她的感情就冒犯了母亲的利益
my soliciting her affections would intrude on the mother's province.
我得说这就是差别
And I would call that...
lsringhausen小姐
a logical distinction, Miss lsringhausen...
与人们的生活方式无关
having nothing to do with the way people live.
[上句意思是 无论母亲什么样 她对自己孩子的爱是
不变的 所以你想到的我也能想到 不用你操心我的孩子]
楼下的人都很惊慌
The people downstairs are scared.
-他们是么? -因为你的话
-Are they? -Of your talk.
他们认为你相信营地处在危险之中
They think you believe the camp's in jeopardy.
我不对误解负责任
I ain't answerable for misinterpretations.
真相就是 Lila 天气正在转好
The truth is, Lila, the weather's getting better...
看起来会暖和一阵子
and it looks to stay mild a spell.
老混蛋Cy又逃过一劫
Old Cy has outlasted the cocksuckers one more time.
如果我是在自欺欺人
If it was in me to kid myself,
那么我会带着它为了证明上帝是爱我们的
I'd take this for a proving God loves me.
-我相信上帝爱我们 -你真的相信 心肝?
-I believe he loves us. -Do you, sweetheart?
是他的手领着我买下你 养大你的么?
Did his hand lead me to buying and turning you out?
那真是个可爱的想法
That's a lovely thought.
你下次祷告时 会加点美言么?
Next you're in touch, would you put the good word in?
我会的
I do.
我每天晚上都为你祈祷
I pray for you every night.
好吧 愚蠢的行为
All right, stupid...
闭上你的嘴吧
time to shut your fucking mouth.
现在闭上你的嘴 然后转过去 闭上眼睛吧
You shut your fucking mouth, now, and turn over and close your eyes.
抬起腿
Lift your leg.
慵懒的样子 敞开私处
Languid and open for adventures.
对你来讲 Atlantis 多露出点乳头
In your case, Atlantis, present the tits a little more.
你能保持半个小时么?
Can you hold that for half an hour?
我已经保持一辈子了
I've been holding this my whole fucking life.
=W先生 -你好
-Mr W. -Hello.
我们还没开门你就来了
You jumped the gun on our opening by half an hour...
但是我们可以为你例外一次
but I believe we can make an exception.
我的合伙人 Joanie.
My partner, Joanie.
-你好 -你好
-How do you do? -How do you do?
去拿我们的新鲜货 巴泽尔的波本威士忌 Joanie
Our caller fancies Basil's bourbon, Joanie...
藏在吧台的地板下面
which is hid beneath the floorboard at the bar.
好的
All right.
-不坐下么? -我不认为我会坐下来
-Won't you sit? -I don't know that I will.
-她去哪了? -Carrie逗留了一下
-Where is she? -Carrie's been detained.
逗留?
Detained?
你不需要我告诉你 Carrie的想法是她自己的事吧
You don't need me telling you Carrie's mind is her own.
我们打了夏延[这是故事背景]  她停下来去看亲戚了
We hit Cheyenne and she stopped to see a relative.
Basil Hayden把自己当广告藏在了地板下
Basil Hayden hid beneath the floorboards as advertised.
你们可以不在我的视野中么?
Would you get out of my sight, please?
她多亲的亲戚在夏延?
How close a relative is she fucking in Cheyenne?
她很快就能来的 W先生
She's coming soon, Mr W.
-她就到了么? -过几天吧
-ls her arrival imminent? -A matter of days.
问题是要过多少天?
How many days are in a matter?
这段时间就不能干点别的么?
Would fucking something else fill the time?
Yeah  你身价多少?
Yeah, how much you cost?
我是非卖品 先生 但陪你免费
I ain't for sale, sir. But I would fuck you for free.
Well 我得说  你不是我喜欢的类型
Well, I have to say, you ain't my type.
你是站在那说 你就是个死人么?
Do you stand there, Mr W,saying you're dead solid sure...
你从来没有诧异过
you'll not ever again be surprised...
直到你完成你的尘世之旅?
till you've completed your earthly course?
有点太自以为是了吧 先生
Ain't that presumptuous, sir?
是不是我们打要价太高了吧  我们明码标价 童叟无欺
And ain't our quoted fee, to surprise you, fair and just?
我从不欠嫖资
I always pay for pussy.
Well 那么我会让你干我的 如果你挽着我过去
Well, I may let you then,if you go ahead and twist my arm.
-你是要额外付钱么? -别碰我
-You pay extra for that? -Do unhand me.
好的 好的 W先生 我不碰你
Aye, aye. Mr W, who I just unhanded...
用不到巴兹尔波本威士忌先生了
and Mr Basil Hayden do not wish to be disturbed.
你想要我回到刚才的位置么?
You want me back where I was?
如果她杀了那个混蛋
If she kills that fucking cocksucker...
我余下的生命就要为此偿债了
I'm gonna be working for the rest of my life.
Richardson, Richardson, Richardson.
我们垂暮不语的岁月什么时候能来到的?
When will come the quiet hours of our declining years?
-我和你说话呢 傻瓜 -我不想听
-I'm talking to you, dimwit. -I wasn't listening.
Richardson,你不坐下来么?
Richardson, won't you sit yourself?
让我帮你干点
Allow me to take up your labours.
我深信 动荡
I am confiding that turbulence...
最猛烈的那种剧变
upheaval of the most violent sort...
好比翻江倒海的巨变
churning seas, waves of a scale and force...
即便最有经验的水手也会呕吐的剧变
to make the most seasoned seafarer vomit...
正在等着这个营地
are in prospect for this camp.
我们 我 你
And we, Richardson, you, l...
以及其他的悲催的人
and, tragically, others...
其他的很多的人
so very many others...
他们跋涉到这里买下土地
who journeyed to the hills to stake their claims...
和土地债权在一起的还有他们的未来
and with those claims their hopes for the future...
所有这些都会被海淹没 沉入水底
are but pawns of the savage sea and playthings of the fucking deep.
很明显我们不会  我们在避风港里
Not for us, apparently, the placid harbour...
在某个航段 接近终点的地方 摇啊摇啊
on which voyages, near complete, to bob and rot...
摇啊摇啊 平静的待着
bob and rot, becalmed.
对于我们来讲  说到底
For us, to the very end...
也不过是要面对暴风雨的剧变 以及它粉碎性的打击
the dizzying surges of the storm and its crashing descents!
你明白我在说什么吗 你个讨人厌的笨蛋
Do you understand me, you repulsive lout?
No.
土地证明 Richardson  要被宣布无效了
The claims, Richardson, they're being overturned.
几乎什么都剩不下
Save those few...
对于那些在流言传播前处理掉财产的人
who dispose off their holdings before word circulates.
穷困显现了
Destitution looms!
Oh  天啊
Oh, dear.
是的 甚至你现在都察觉到形势了
Yes, yes. Even you now recognise the situation.
Oh WELL
Oh, well.
休息吧 Richardson.
Take the rest of the night off, Richardson.
多谢  先生
Thank you, sir.
别和别人说
But confide in no one...
关于土地证明的事
about the claims!
我都脱光了会不会有意思点
Would we have even more fun naked?
或者我脱 你别脱
Or I could, and you could stay dressed.
或者反过来
Or the opposite.
-我是谁? -W先生
-Who am l? -You're Mr W.
你的老板在康斯托克和墨西哥受到了更大的损失
Your boss struck bigger than anyone in the Comstock and Mexico.
所以你来到这里给营地带来了曙光
So you being here puts a shine to this camp's prospects.
帮我解扣子
Unbutton my shirt.
好的 先生
Yes, sir.
-别看我的脸 -那就不看 先生
-Do not look at my face. -No, sirree.
-我应该告诉你我为谁工作么? -你随便
-Shall I tell you who I work for? -As you wish.
要是你告诉我了 我是不是过会儿要更卖力的伺候你
If you do, how shall I occupy myself while you're doing it?
和我没说的时候一样就行
The same as if I don't.
依我了?
For me to judge?
你随便
As you wish.
你上衣的扣子就是你最大的资本了?
Your shirt buttons are your big interest?
还是说我们把这些也解开
Or shall we advance to these buttons here?
我要试试我以前没用过的方法取悦你么?
and shall I hazard an approach I rarely find ill-received?
不用
No.
我试个方法  我不记得拒绝过的方法
Shall I hazard an approach, l, myself, I never remember refusing?
你愿意指教一下我么?
And will you supervise closely?
W先生 我就当你同意了
Mr W, I am gonna take that as a yes.
不 应该是当做我不同意
No, take it as a no.
烦人
Nuts.
你的聪明的脑袋没有发挥的空间啊！
What a tiny corner of operation for such an amusing mind.
我要说 我待在这
I'll promise as I sojourn here...
给你讲点男人世界的事吧
to bring you stories of the world of men.
我却身处女人世界之中 挥霍着自己
I'll just be here in my girl's world, diddling myself.
我知道你带武器进来的
I admire you coming armed.
我要把这个 穿过你的尿道送入你的膀胱 AI
I'm gonna pass this through your penis up into your bladder, Al...
我只对你说一次
and I'm gonna say this to you once...
我对此造成的痛苦表示抱歉
I'm sorry for how it hurts.
-该死的 压住他 别让他动 -以圣母的名义
-God damn it, hold him still! -Mother of God!
救救我 以圣母的名义
Help me! Mother of God!
该死的 Johnny 进去帮他啊
Fuck you, Johnny! Get in there and fucking help him!
我能做什么?
What am I supposed to do?
把你的手放在他嘴边 让他咬住你
Put your hand in his mouth! Let him bite your fucking hand!
好了 AI 我插进膀胱了 我听到石头声了
All right, Al, I'm in your bladder. I can hear the fucking stone.
我试着移动石头以便你能排尿
I'm gonna try now to move the stone to release your water...
你使劲 如果你能
so you push now, if you can, son.
Oh 圣母啊 帮帮我吧
Oh, God! Mother, take me!
如果你还行就使劲尿出来
Push now if you can, get your water flowing.
我在使劲 帮我一把 上帝啊
I'm trying! Help me! Christ!
如果不成大功 我就杀了你 医生
I'll fucking kill you, Doc!
-把那个给我拿出来 -闭嘴
-Just take it out of him! -Shut up!
好了 我看见
All right, I can see...
尿伴随着血出来了 很好
some fucking urine with the blood. Good for you.
他好了么?治愈了?
Is he all right now? Is he cured now?
-有效果了 -不管咋样 起作用了 医生?
-It's fucking something, anyway. -ls that something, anyway, Doc?
好的 AI
All right, Al...
我要拿出来了 你忍住 不会有多痛
I'm gonna take it out of you. You hold on and it won't hurt so bad.
他拿出了点东西南北  Trixie.
He put something out of himself, Trixie.
现在 不管咋样 有效果了
Now, that's something, anyway.
出来了?
Is it out of him?
Well 器械出来了
Well, that instrument's out of him.
石头呢?
And what of the fucking stone?
我没看见石头出来
I didn't see no fucking stone come out.